When I throw a jab or a straight,
it always lands
But when I'm aiming for your heart,
I miss every time
Parallel, zigzagging, awkward, incoherent
When you look my way and move closer to me
I know it doesn't mean the same thing for you
But I wish we could stay like this forever
My changing feelings are driving me crazy
The moment you turn to face me,
take that! Telepathy
If only we could feel the same thing
I want to kick this pesky subtlety away
I want to know everything,
I want to know everything
I can't fool you forever
I can't keep this hidden
I want to shout out my secret, AHHH
Take that! Telepathy
Te-te-te-telepathy
Telepathy
Birthday
Present
"Birthday Present."
Here. For you.
Huh?
You wanted these, right?
Thanks! But why?
Today's your birthday, remember?
Oh, yeah! I guess it is!
I'm older than you now!
Show me some respect!
Every single year... This gets so old.
Mornin', Misuzu!
Good mor—
What are those?
Jun just gave them to me!
My birthday present! Pretty cool, right?
So yeah, I went ahead and turned 16 first!
Indeed. Happy birthday.
You're welcome to call me
"Onee-san" if you want.
Every single year... This gets so old.
Here.
From me.
Wow, really? Thanks!
Oh, it's pretty heavy. What's in it?
Reference books.
Th-Thanks...
I'm so glad you like it.
Happy birthday, dear—
Wait!
Wait, wait, wait!
Um... What is this?
It's gold.
I have a bigger one at home,
but it was too heavy to carry to school.
I'm happy, but... this is
definitely too much.
Would you be interested in putting
that wealth of yours to use?
Misuzu-chan!
No!
Don't team up with her!
Tomo, want to come over
to my house this weekend?
We're gonna give you a big transformation!
Saturday
What's all this about transforming me?
You're gonna dress me up like you
did the day I went out with Jun?
First, you're putting on this skirt.
A skirt?!
Put this on, too.
A hairpiece?!
A wig.
So... what does all this mean?
It means we're using this opportunity
to make you as feminine as possible.
So I'm gonna dress like a girl?!
You say that as if you're not a girl.
Well? Aren't you done yet?
We're still on the basics.
It's kind of a weird feeling, though.
What is?
Me wearing makeup, I mean.
If I did it right,
could I have a pretty face like this, too?
Take over.
'Kay!
Huh?
H-H-How do I look?
You're pretty, Tomo-chan!
Indeed.
R-Really?!
Since we've done all this,
try talking more like a girl, too.
More like a girl? But I don't know how to...
Just start by speaking more politely.
H-Hello. My name is Aizawa Tomo.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Am I doing this right?
You're super cute!
Indeed. Boys would probably like it.
Huh?!
I don't think you could make
friends with them, though.
You'd just be a thorn in their sides.
What's that supposed to mean?
I'm suddenly craving some ice cream.
Me, too.
Oh, I'll go buy some, then.
You've both done a lot for me, after all.
Really?
Sorry to make you do this.
Don't worry about it!
Just... let me change fir—
Wha—
Hey! Are you seriously making
me go out dressed like this?!
Absolutely.
There's no point in dressing like that
if we're the only ones who see it.
Yeah, but...
Off you go.
I wish you luck.
Hey! Misuz—
Damn those two!
They're staring at me!
I guess I really do look weird!
Wait, Jun?!
What do I do?! What excuse can
I give for being dressed like this?!
H-Huh?
Not sure what that's about, but...
if he doesn't recognize me, I'm golden!
I'll just buy my stuff and get outta here!
There's no way. There's no damn way.
Okay! I gotta get away from here quick!
Whoa, are you okay?
Her face looks just like Tomo's,
but she doesn't wear stuff like this. She doesn't wear makeup, either.
If this is Tomo, I don't... I mean...
I can't.
Do you need a hand?
Wh-What is this soft touch he's using?
Whoa...
Are you okay?
Why is he treating me like this?
Well, I'll be going now.
U-Um...
Would you mind if I walked
with you... for a while?
What the heck was I thinking?!
What do I do now?!
Now that we're walking together,
I'm sure of it.
This girl isn't Tomo.
Tomo's a little shorter than she is.
Um, please don't look at me so much.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I really do look strange, don't I?
Even I realize that.
Huh?
No, I think you just look pretty.
Today's the day I die, isn't it?!
That's it!
There you go!
You got it!
Way to go!
Here I go!
That kid's pretty good.
Go, go!
That's it! Go!
Shoot!
Aw, so close!
Huh?
I'm sorry. I like watching sports and such.
That's surprising.
I get all fired up when I watch them.
That's not very ladylike, is it?
I don't know if it's ladylike or not,
but I like people like that.
What's with him today?!
Is he trying to kill me?!
Those two are pretty good, aren't they?
Huh? Oh... Yes, they do stand out.
They're clearly good friends.
Even though they're a boy and a girl...
What do you think will happen
to them in the future?
Huh? Well, uh...
I-It'd be nice if they became
boyfriend and girlfriend.
I figured you'd say that.
Huh?!
I have someone like that, too.
A girl who's... basically my best friend.
But lately, things aren't the same
as they were when we were kids.
How would you like things to
turn out with her in the future?
Well, I haven't really
given it much thought.
Well, you need to think about it!
My goal for the time being is...
to beat her, I guess.
Be—
At this point... should I just tell him?
I'll tell him I'm Tomo!
Then maybe he'll see me
as a little bit more...
Um, there's something I've been wondering...
Huh?!
You bought ice cream at the
convenience store. Is it okay out here?
Oh, crap!
Th-Thank you so much for all you've done today!
Uh, hang on...
I'd better be going now!
It couldn't be... right?
Sorry I took so long!
A lot happened on the... way...
Happy Birthday
Tomo-chan
This homemade cake is really good!
Thanks, both of you!
Forget about that. Did you really see
Junichiro at the convenience store?
Oh, yeah...
He said I looked pretty.
Wow! That's great!
Well... If I'm being honest,
I was super happy when he said it.
But I guess what I really want to
hear him say is something else.
You mean you'd rather be
called cute than pretty?
Let's try for that next time.
Uh, no, that's not what I meant...
What?
That hurt, damn it!
What the hell are you doing?!
Yeah, that's right.
That punch could only come from Tomo!
Why are you happy?!
A-Are you some kinda freak?!
Burn Up!
The Ball Sports Tournament
"Burn Up! The Ball Sports Tournament."
Damn. I missed.
Hey! Why are you running away?
Tomo-chan is kinda scary.
Because the class-versus-class ball
sports tournament is coming up.
She's always like that
before an athletic event.
Uh, so... For certain reasons...
Aizawa-san will be on the boys' dodgeball
team at the ball sports tournament.
All right!
This is awesome, Tomo! We can play together!
Why did this happen again?!
The Day of the Ball Sports Tournament
First Round
I heard there's a girl on the team
we're playing in the first round.
For real? This'll be a cakewalk!
We're ready!
Ready!
Sure, we'll play around with ya.
And we'll be giving this all we've got.
You'd better make sure you're prepared.
VS. Third-Year Punk Team
Instant Victory
Second Round
Let's have a good, fair match!
Yeah.
I know I don't have to hold
back against you, Senpai!
Let's make it a good game.
Wha...
Everyone, put your own
safety above all else!
Let's finish this match with
everyone still standing!
What're you talking about?
It's just a dodgeball match.
Misaki!
VS. Misaki-senpai and His Classmates
Overwhelming Victory
Well, the final round's next.
Yeah.
Hey! We've got trouble!
One of the guys on the other team
in the finals is like a gorilla!
That third-year in the judo club,
Goma Takeru-senpai, right?
The guy known as the strongest
kid in the school.
I'm not sure if even Jun and I can beat him.
I knew the day would come eventually
when we'd have to fight him...
But I didn't think we'd have
to fight him this soon.
Uh, no... You don't really
have to fight him.
What are you saying? He's the
strongest kid in the school!
We've gotta fight him at least once!
Sorry. I don't get you at all.
Too bad we lost at volleyball.
There was no way a team with
you and me on it could win.
True.
It's just about time for Tomo
and Junichiro's final round.
What are you snickering about?
I was just thinking, you and I
are together a lot lately.
Hey, don't go.
Final Round
We'll be giving everything
we've got to this final round.
Yep!
So you're Aizawa Tomo?
Yeah, that's me.
I heard you were the karate club's ace,
but frankly, I'm disappointed.
I didn't know you'd be such
a fragile-looking little lady.
"A fragile-looking little lady," he says!
Did you hear that?! Well?!
You do seem fairly strong...
But to be honest, you interest
me more than Aizawa.
Pardon?
I hear you're pretty athletic,
but you're not in any clubs.
How about this? If I win this
match, you join the judo club.
Fine. And if I win...
What should I say?
Way to fall flat at the
finish line! Don't ask me!
The final round of boys'
dodgeball will now begin.
Misuzu-chan is cheering me on!
Watch me. I'll win this match for you!
Tanabe!
He was sending you some sort of sign.
Was he? I wasn't watching.
He didn't waste any time!
Hey, Tanabe! You okay?!
Sports are great, aren't they?
It doesn't matter if you hurt someone,
as long as you follow the rules.
Damn that violent bastard!
What does he think sports are about?!
I don't think he's one to talk.
You can say that again.
Noda!
Fukaya!
Why aren't you throwing the ball at me?!
Don't be impatient.
I took out the guys who aren't fit
to stand on this court first.
And that means you're next, Aizawa!
Uh-oh!
Jun!
You idiot! What the hell were you doing?!
Dunno. My body just moved on its own.
Stay with me, Jun!
How dare you do that to Jun?
I'm gonna make you pay for that!
Oh? And how are you gonna make me pay?
It's down to a one-on-one between
Aizawa-san and the gorilla.
Is Aizawa-san gonna be okay?
Don't worry. No one can beat her.
I'm putting my all into this throw!
Here I go!
Take this, damn it!
Bring it on!
It dropped?! A between-the-legs pass?!
I'm not playing by myself here!
Go, Jun!
Huh?
Yah.
That concludes the match.
The boys' dodgeball winner is Class 1-A!
Congratulations.
Everyone, give Class 1-A
a round of applause!
Tomo-chan, congrats on the win.
Yeah, thanks.
What's wrong? You don't seem happy.
I had so much fun being
on a team with him today.
It was like we went back to the old days.
It kinda made me wish things
could stay like this forever.
I hope we can always have the kind of
relationship where we can goof around together.
But I guess we can't, huh?
Sorry, Tomo.
In the end, I can only do
things for my own gain.
Hey. Hold up.
You're not satisfied with
how that ended, are you?
Come with me for a minute.
Wh-What's the idea?! Why...
Why am I getting beat up by you,
when I do judo and you do karate?!
You let your guard down too much.
I managed to pull off more wins than him.
Damn it... I guess I still
can't beat you after all.
Is this really an outcome you
should be depressed over?
Huh?
You didn't even use karate on me once.
At this point, we might as well say I lost.
That's not the problem.
Hang on!
I hear you almost never
enter any tournaments.
Don't you feel like that's
a waste of talent?
What was your reason for getting so strong?
I just wanted to catch up to the
big back I saw in front of me.
But the situation changed,
and now I don't even know
how to approach it.
What do you think I should do?
Uh... I don't know.
I heard you fought with Goma-senpai.
Yeah, and I lost.
I see.
I lost, but I bet you could beat him.
You know, I've thought this for a while,
but you overestimate me way too much.
Do I? I don't think I'm overestimating you.
Then again, it wouldn't surprise
me if you started breathing fire.
Oh, you're finally counting
me as a monster, huh?
You're a guy, and I'm a girl.
You're obviously gonna be better than
me at any kind of physical contest.
During that match, I wasn't
expecting that pass at all.
I just believed that you
would win it in the end.
Maybe I'm still just a gamer kid who's only
strong-willed because you're by my side.
It's not physical strength.
What's up?
Oh, nothing.
I want...
to be like you.
(This suspicious behavior is...)
Hey, you know, I'm all mixed up
It's too complicated, I'm freaking out
I want to look cute to you
(crazy, crazy, drive me crazy, and that's…)
So I'm plotting, bargaining,
sly, and stubborn
Dizzying love
Just tell him to look at you
And watch him stiffen up even more,
because you're both so awkward
What? Even if we're alike in that way
It doesn't make me happy, 'cause it
means our love is going nowhere
Cloudy heart, swirling emotions—
I sense rain coming
So I partly open my umbrella,
then sneakily scoot closer to you
Please notice the curl of my
eyelashes as I keep blinking
And don't say I'm acting weird
All this plotting and bargaining
is my sly plan to look cute to you
Try to solve the riddle of
this soft, dizzying love
(Buzzing, fidgeting)
Listen, I might be a bit
tangled in my own web now
But once you unravel the mystery,
you'll see pure lo-love